What do you think that cloud looks like?
I think the cloud looks like a tennis ball.
Well, I think it looks like a golf ball.
Tennis ball.
Golf ball.
Tennis ball!
Golf ball!
Bulleh.
Oh my oxygen, Rocky has some serious vomiting issues.
Yeah, but when he has to barf,
he knows exactly where to.
Grr!
Guys, why do you slap each other? It's pointless.
He's a jerk.
Hey, what is that speaker machine doing here?
I'm here to remind you that your team, Another Name, lost.
Let's go to the Cake at Stake place to see who'll be eliminated.
[laughter]
The two of you with the most votes will leave the team.
One will join the Cherries.
The other will be eliminated.
Golf Ball and Firey, you each have a Win Token.
Would you like to use it now?
Hmm...
Remember, if you use it, half of your votes will not count.
I won't use it.
Well, I will.
Out of the total thirty-seven votes,
Tennis Ball is safe at two votes.
Yay!
But don't I also get some cake?
A cake was too expensive, so we'll pretend.
Here's an imaginary slice of cake.
[splat]
Firey is safe at three votes...
Grr!
...and Coiny is safe at five votes.
Golf Ball and Rocky got twelve and fifteen votes, respectively.
Even with her Win Token,
Golf Ball's still in the top two.
What!?
Uh-oh, I'm left with the slappers!
Golf Ball and Rocky,
the Squishy Cherries will either vote you onto their team...
...or to be eliminated.
So, yeah. I'd pick Rocky onto our team.
GB is just a no-no!
I'd say Rocky,
because Golf Ball sounds like a boy,
even though she's a girl,
and that's just wrong!
I'd say Rocky,
because Golf Ball's a bossy-bot.
I'd say, like, Rocky,
because I am not a big fan of dimples.
I'd say Rocky,
because GB said my brain is small!
Well, what I say won't matter,
so I'll say Rocky too!
Goodbye, Golf Ball,
or GBGB, for short.
Hyuck, hyuck, that's so hilare!
Now my chances of winning went from
7.143 percent...
...to 0.000 percent!
It's narrowed down to thirteen contestants.
...a baker's dozen.
I wonder where the new stairs lead.
Well, in order for the next contest to start,
all of you must climb them.
[♫]
I...
...I think this is the top.
Whoa!
Ha, ha.
[♫]
So, now that you're all up here except for that clumsy Tennis Ball,
I want you to tie these balloons around your waists.
[♫]
Now that you're done,
would you like to see a magic trick?
Yeah, I love magic tricks. Do it!
Okay, here I go.
Poof.
[scream]
...oh. Uh.
Ha, ha.
So the eleventh contest is to try to stay up in the air.
Last team standing wins.
Well, this should be easy.
Oh yeah, over there is a basket of nails to throw at others.
Help yourself and begin.
Okay, I say we go for the Cherries.
With seven people, they're a bigger threat.
Okay. [grunt]
[grunt]
It just doesn't feel right.
No, Bubble, that's because you have to pull tighter!
[grunt]
Grr!
Whoa!
[screaming]
[scream]
Hi, TB.
Whoa!
[grunt]
What was that for?
The balloons were pink.
Pink is too girly!
I would disagree.
I think pink is quite manly.
But our team color is red.
Shouldn't our balloons be red, not pink?
Well, red balloons were too expensive.
[scream]
Oh no, Firey, you lit my fuse!
Oh, you're down here, too?
That means it's all down to Coiny!
The jerk!
[grunt]
Leafy, watch out!
Huh?
Whoa!
Yah.
Oh, I'm an ice-cold killer.
Oh my gosh, oh my gosh, oh my gosh, oh my gosh, oh my gosh...
Die, Coiny.
Uh-oh!
This basket will protect me!
The Names lose again.
Oh, no!
[explosion]
So how do we pop without nails?
Um...
We bite!
[grunt]
[pop]
No!
Mweh.
[pop]
[scream]
I'm gonna try what the talking metal box did.
Poof.
Yeah, we won!
So, the Grapes won,
the Cherries got number two,
and the Names lost again.
Voters,
Vote off either, Firey, or Tennis Ball.
The two with the most votes will leave the team.
One will join the Grapes.
Um, maybe we should go down now.
Nah.